hey guys so many people requested this
problem my DMs were flooded with this
one so I guess we got to do it it's
asking for the area of this shaded
region this region is a rectangle so the
area is going to be base time height
where the base is this right here and
the height is equal to 10 we don't know
the length of the base yet so let's call
it X so if we copy down the arrow we
know this entire distance right here is
equal to 14 and since this piece is X
that means this remaining piece is going
to be 14 - x and we have the same thing
going on right here this whole entire
distance is equal to 8 this is X which
leaves 8 - x for this piece the length
of the base of this larger rectangle is
equal to 20 so we can say 8 - x + x + 14
- x is equal to 20 and now we can solve
for x so first we'll combine like terms
this negative X and this positive X can
cancel each other out and we can bring
down thisx we can combine the 8 plus the
14 to give us 22 and this is all going
to be equal to 20 we can subtract 22
from both sides on the left hand side we
havex and on the right hand side 20 - 22
is -2 so we havex is equal to -2 that
means that X is equal to pos2 so let's
update this x to 2 and now we're ready
to find the area of our region it's
going to be the base times the height
where the base is equal to 2 and the
height is equal to 10 and that's going
to give us 20 square units and that's
the answer to our question let's put a
box around it how exciting